Guide to the Ernest J. Sternglass papers, [ca. 1952-2008]
Sternglass, Ernest J. papers
- Alphabetical File List
  - Evolution - Cosmology and Biology, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Evolution - Man and All Life, 1974-1979 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Extinctions, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Extra-Terrestrial Intelligence. Search and Possible Evidence For, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Fallout, Effects on Dental Caries, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Fallout Measurements, 1957-1958, US, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Fallout Paths From New Mexico. Critique, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Fallout. Recent (China and France), 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Federal Radiation Council (FRC) Guides, Milk, Sr, I, Ca, pH of Water. Guides and Removal, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Federation of American Scientists (FAS) Newsletter. Fallout, Nuclear Safety, etc., 1973-1981 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Fertility and Fallout, 1971-1982 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Fertility and Nuclear Tests. Alternative to Rindfuss, 1954-1978 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Fish Data. Total Catches I, 1969-1994 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Fish Data. Total Catches II, 1969-1994 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Fish and Marine Life Reproduction and Population Effects of Radiation and Doses, Concentration, 1960-1984 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Fish. Radiation Doses and Effects. Peru, 1969-1983 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Fish Reproduction and Fallout, 1968-1983 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Fluorescent Scanning, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Food Additives and Cancer. Delaney Clause, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Food Irradiation, 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Ford, G. President Advisors and Science Policy, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Forest Damage. Nuclear Reichelt, 1983-1992 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Franke, Bernd, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Freedom of Public. In Politics and Science, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Freedom of Scientific Publication - AAAS Letter, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - French Nuclear Power Program, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Frigerio, N. A., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Fulbright Fellowship Application, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Fusion, 1971-1980 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Gamma Camera Development and Relevant Materials, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Gary, Robert, Esq., 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Gas From Nuclear Detonation (Gasbuggy), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Gas. Natural Supply, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - General Electric Reactor Emissions Report, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Genetic Effects of Atomic Tests and Nukes. 1978 NRC Study (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Genetic Effects of Radiation. DNA Mass, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Genetics vs. Development. Radiation Effects. Drafts, 1968-1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Geography (Nuclear). Map of Nuclear Threat, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Georgia Mortality (Savannah River Incident Data), 1971-1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Gerende Shipping Port. Paper on Prematurity (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Giere, Ron, 1970-1979 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Gillberg, Bjorn, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Gofman, J Publications, 1975-1982 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Gofman and Tamplin I, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Gofman and Tamplin II, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Goodman, Leo. Nuclear Accidents, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Gordon Conference - 1976 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Gould Jay's Draft. '92-'93, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Gravel, Mike. Releases on Radiation, Cancer, Energy Alternatives, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Gray Panthers, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Greenpeace, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Griffith's Aliquippa Story (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Ground Zero, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Group Against Smog And Pollution (GASP), 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Grunbaum, A, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Hanford. 1969 Paper, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Hanford. 1972 Paper. Draft and Data, 1968-1972 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Hanford. 1972 Paper. Epidemiological Studies of Fallout and Patterns of Cancer Mortality, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Hanford. 1974 Paper on Immune Response and Radiation, 1967-1974 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Hanford. 1974 Paper. Notes and Preliminary Draft, 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Hanford. 1983-1984 Accident, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Hanford. Contamination of Columbia River, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Hanford Downwinder. % LBN PATP for Report, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Hanford Health Effects Study. 1986 Proposal, 1985-1994 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Hazards of Electromagnetic Radiation on Ordnance (HERO) (Nuclear Weapon Accidents and Effects) Empress II Stories. Greenland, 1985-1988 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Helath Food Paper, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Health Physics Society, 1968-1972 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Health Physics Society Attacks, 1969-1979 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Heart Disease, 1965-1974 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Heart Disease, Atherosclerosis. Radiation, Dose Rate Experiments. Humans and Animals, 1964-1988 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Heart Disease and Cancer. Radiation Data for US, 1967-1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Heart Disease in New York City and Fallout, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Heart Disease and Radiation I, 1960-1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Heart Disease and Radiation II, 1966-1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Heart Disease. Radiation and Environment. Trace Elements and Radioactivity, 1964-1967 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Heart Disease and Radiation. References, 1968-1992 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Heart Disease and Radiataion (Sr, Po, etc), 1964-1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Heart Disease and Trace Elements. Epidemiology Evidence, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Heavy Ions. Acceleration for Medical Purposes, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Heidelberg, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Heidelberg Study. 1978, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Herrmann, Henry, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - High Voltage. Biological Hazards, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Hiroshima Data, 1964-1975 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Hiroshima. Infant Mortality. In Utero Exposure, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - History of Nuclear Physics, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - History and Philosophy of Science, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - History, Recent. Summaries: 1968 etc., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Hoffman, Pat, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Home Furnishing and Improvement. Ideas and Clippings (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Home, Sale, Purchase, Construction, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Honicker Petition, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Honicker vs. Hendrie. Reply to NRC, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Honicker vs. Hendrie. Reply to NRC Staff, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Hormonal Effects on Prenatal Development, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Huen, Al. PhD Thesis and Relevant Materials, 1961-1973 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Hull, A. P. Reports and Attacks, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Human Development. Biological Effects on, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Humanities Perspective on Technoogy, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Humboldt (California) Area. Cancer, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Huver, Charles, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Hydrogen Bomb Secret (Progress), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Hypertension, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Illinois. Vitality Statistics. 169-1974 (Dresden), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Image Detection. Theory, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Immune System. Effects on. Radiation. Plants and Animals, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - India (Bhopal) Chemical Disaster (December 1984), 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Infant Mortality and Cognitive Defects. Uranium Mining, 1980-1985 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Infant Mortality. Lung Problem Origin, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Infant Mortality. Trends in Europe and USSR 1970-1975, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Infectious Disease and Fallout. 1976 Summary, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Infectious Disease and Fallout. Reye's Syndrome, Rabies, etc., 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Infectious Disease and Radiation. Influenza, etc. Data for New York City, US and other., 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Inflation and Nuclear Weapons (Construction and Test), 1981 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Inglis, David. Review of My Book, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Interdisciplinary Education, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Investment Possibilities, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Iodine 131, 129 etc. Data and Effects (For Book II), 1971-1982 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Iodine 131. Fetal Concentrations, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Iodine 131, 125. Thyroid Damage. Low Dose Rates, 1969-1983 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Ireland. Data, Dublin Trip, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Ireland, Dublin Symposium, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Irish Transport Workers Union (John Carrol). Seminar and Lecture 5/12/1978 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Japan Cancer Statistics, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Japanese Anti-Bomb Movements, 1974-1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Japanese Anti-Nuclear Movement, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Johnson, Carl, 1978-1984 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Johnson and Johnson, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Joint Atomic Energy Commission. Testimony March 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Jones, Dorothy, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Journals (Possible Places for Publications), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Journals. Science. Instructions for Authors, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Judaism, Hasidism and Science Reconstruction. Buber and Kaplan, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Keller, J. Romnes Case, 1974-1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Keller, J. Shippingport Worker Leukemia Case. Intoduction by Defendant, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Kelly, Petra, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Kentucky Nuclear Waste Maxiflats, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Kepford, Chauncey. Testimony, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Kerala, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Kidney Disease and Radiation (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Knapr, H. Nevada Sheep Deaths and Thyroid Dose Call, 1983-1990 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Koertge, Noretta (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Lapp, Ralph, 1971-1980 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Lasers, Radiation Damage, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Lave, L. B., Leinhardt and Kaye. 1972 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Lead Poisoning and Decline of Rome (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Lecture Planning, Public (Speaker's Bureau), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Lectures, Popolar. Astronomy, Cosmology, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Lee, Jane, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Legal Action Against AEC, 1970-1978 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Legal Battle Against Nuclear Release, 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Leukemia, 1963-1981 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Leukemia. Childhood. My 1963 Article (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Leukemia Data. Allegheny County, 1968-1972 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Leukemia Data. Beaver and Nearry Counties, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Leukemia Data. Western Pennsylvania (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Leukemia and Environmental Radiation. 1977-1978. Recent Confirmations. Fallout and Nuclear, 1978-1984 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Leukemia Papers, 1957-1980 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Lewis, Richard. Papers (Shippingport), 1973 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Limerick Testimony. November 1973 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Lions Grant. Electronic Imaging, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Little, J. B. Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Low Dose-Rate Effects. Summary of Recent Lab Evidence on Low Dose Rate, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Low Dose-Rate Radiation Effects in Animals - Dogs, Rats, Hamsters, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Low Level Animal Population Exposure, 1967-1973 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Low-Level Radiation Activity of Sr90 and Y90, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Low Level Radiation Articles, 1973-1979 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Low-Level Radiation. Curves and Transparancies, 1969-1981 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Low Level Radiation Effects, 1962-1981 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Low Level Radiation Effects. References, 1976-1983 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Low Level Radiation Lectures, 1960-1981 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Low Level Radiation. White House Task Force. February 1979 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Macleod, Gordon, 1979-1984 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Madoff, Michelle (Her Group) (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Maine. Yankee. Closing Effort, 1981-1984 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Maine Yankee Studies, 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Mammography Grant Application, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Mancuso. Original Hanford Study Results, 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Mancuso Report and Correspondence. 1977, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Mancuso: Smitherman, 1975-1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Maps of US (Blank) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Marble Hill Intervention. 1983, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Marshall, David. Ecology Manual, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Martell, 1975-1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Maternal Mortality and Fallout. US 1930-1978, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Mays, C. W. Papers on Cancer, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Medical Tribune. Article on Infant Mortality and Fallout, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Medical Xrays. Risks vs. Benefits, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Mental Development and Sex Differences. Maturation, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Mental Illness. Genetic Cause and Radiation, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Membrane Damage Paper, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Membrane. Effects of Radiation on Membrane and Heart Disease, 1974-1980 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Membrane Paper (Draft in Process), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Membrane Paper. Healh Physics Society. October 1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Membrane Paper 1974-Preparation, 1963-1974 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Membrane. Radiation Effects I, 1957-1974 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Membrane. Radiation Effects II, 1960-1983 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Memory - Physiological Mechanisms, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Merck Incinerator. 1992, 1990-1994 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Mercury, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Metzger, Peter, 1971-1976 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Michelson, Irving. Sr-90 in Milk and Diet, 1960-1973 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - microwave radiation. Low Dose Effects, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Midland Reactor Intervention, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Midland Test and Material, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Milk Contamination (Battle Plans 1989), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Millstone Data and Report, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Millstone Environment, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Minnesota. June 1980 Hearings (Prairie Island Spent Fuel, Fabrikant) (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Minnesota Pollution Control Proposal, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Minnesota Reactors, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Minnesota Story. Monticello Plant (Minnesota and Mecca), 1972 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Mississippi Fetal Death Data 1950's (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Missouri Nuclear Plant Protest. Trial and Testimony, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Moeller, D. W. Health Physics. 21. July 1971, p.1 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Molecular Biology. Resources and Instruments. International Labs, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Moratorium. Nuclear, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Morgan, K. Z., 1975-1981 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Moriyama. Papers, 1964-1969 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Morrion, Philip, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Mortality (Adult and Infant) in US. Patterns and Radiation. Moriyama, 1964-1976 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Moskalev - Low Dose Effects of Pu, Ce, etc. (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Moss, Clyde (Student), 1972-1975 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Motz, Joe, 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Motz, Lloyd, 1973-1983 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Muller, H. J. (Geneticist), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Nader and Critical Mass, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Najarian. Portsmouth Navy, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP). Pro-Nuclear State, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - National Heart, Lung and Blood Institute (NHLBI). 1980-Computed Equalization Radiography (CER) Proposal (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - National Science Foundation. Proposal for Statistical Studies of Health Effects, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Natural Food, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Natural Killer Cells and Low Level Radiation, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Natural Radioactivity in Man - Ra, Po, Pb, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Naval Reactors, Releases, etc., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Neuroscience, AIDS, etc., 2000 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Nevada Area Fallout (Gamma-Dose), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Nevada Sheep Trial, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - New Mexico, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - New Mexico. Congenital Defects (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - New Mexico Trip- "Trinitite Scandal", 1967-1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - New Scientist. Three Mile Island (TMI) Article, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - New York City. Disease and Radiation Data, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - New York City Health Data and Radiation Levels, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - New York State Nuclear Facilities, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - New York State Nuclear Facilities Emissions, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - New York State Study. Nuclear Facilities, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - New York Times. Letter Drafts (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - New York Times. Letter May 23, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Neyman, J. Proposed Study (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Nine Mile Point. 1989 Study (Jean Kessner) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Nixon and Watergate Consequences, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - No Nuclear News, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Nuclear Accidents Analysis. Sandia. November 1, 1982 (NIRS Has Full Copy), 1999 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Nuclear Accidents. Plants in New York, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Nuclear Danger. Ideas for Article. 1974, 1969-1977 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Nuclear Energy History, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Nuclear Facicilities in the United States. Maps and Lists (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Nuclear History. Reactors. United States and International, 1970-1990 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Nuclear Industry. Criticism of My Findings (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Nuclear Industry Propaganda - TMI, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Nuclear Information and Resource Service (NIRS), 1981 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Nuclear Medicine Review, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Nuclear Navy. US and USSR, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Nuclear Opponents. Organizations Against Nuclear Tests and Reactors, 1972-1981 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Nuclear Plant. Byron, Illinois. 7/82 Affidavit, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Nuclear Plants. Locations World Wide, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Nuclear Plant Records, 1971-1988 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Nuclear Plant Recycling of Contaminated Parts and Steel, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Nuclear Part Star-Ups, 1991-1999 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Nuclear Power Battle I, 1968-1973 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Nuclear Power Battle II, 1969-1992 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Nuclear Power. The Economic Failure. Komanoff 1992 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Nuclear Power Emissions ('91), 1992 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Nuclear Power Future (Including Space) July/August 1987 Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1987-1997 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Nuclear Power Production in US Relative to Other Sources, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Nuclear Power. Pros and Cons Citizen Groups. National Intervenors, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Nuclear Power Safety Report 1984-1985, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Nuclear Projects. News 1973 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Nuclear Radiation Effects on Fish and Other Amphibians, 1989-1994 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Nuclear Radiation Effects. Trees (Palms). Vermont Trees, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Nuclear Radiation Studies. Federal Radiation Council Reports ('61-'62), 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Nuclear Reactor. Conversion to Gas, 1974-1978 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Nuclear Reactor Costs, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Nuclear Reactor. Dry Cask Fuel Storage Problem, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Nuclear Reactor Hazards: Spent Fuel, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Nuclear Reactor Heath Effects Study. Lambert and Cornell July/August 1980 Archives of Envirnomental Health (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Nuclear Reactor Releases, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Nuclear Reactors in Eastern Europe and USSR, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Nuclear Reactors. 1972 Population Dose Calculations, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Nuclear Reactors Safety, 1982-1990 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Nuclear Reactors in Space, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Nuclear Reactors in US (1973 Map), 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Nuclear Reactors in US. Listing (Including the Reactor Near Washington DC), 1986-1990 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission. 10 CFR 20. 1991 Revision (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC) New Radiation Regulations (1986) (May 11, 1986 Deadline), 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC) Nureg 1.109, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC) 1984 Preliminary Notifications (PNO) (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC) Publication, 1990-2000 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC) Radiation Revision Memorandum. Extra Copies, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC) Report, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Nuclear Releases and Dying Fish, Seals and Dolphins in Coastal Waters, Great Lakes, Ships, 1971-1993 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Nuclear Releases. Effects on Birds, 1988-1992 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Nuclear Releases. Effects on Marine Life, Estuary. Fish (See Also Chernobyl Files), 1983-1994 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Nuclear Releases 1974-1984 (England, R. W. and E. P. Mitchell. Natural Resources Journal. 30, 538. 1990), 1983-1990 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Nuclear vs. Renewable Energy. 1990 Report (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Nuclear Safety, 1971-1991 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Nuclear Safety Report 1984-1986 and Purey Problem Clippings, 1981-1989 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Nuclear Test Ban and Verification (1994) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Nuclear Testing. Climate Effects. Ecology. House and Nuclear Fission Gases. See Also: Radiation Effects on Water, 1981-1992 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Nuclear Testing. Earth Temperature Change and Food Supply, 1971-1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Nuclear Tests, 1968-1993 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Nuclear Tests. Chinese Fallout Episode, 1977-1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Nuclear Tests and Climate. Articles, 1959-1996 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Nuclear Tests and Earthquakes, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Nuclear Tests. Effects on Temperature and Climate I, 1970-1996 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Nuclear Tests. Effects on Temperature and Climate II, 1970-1996 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Nuclear Tests. Effects on Temperature and Climate III, 1970-1996 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Nuclear Tests. Underground Leaks, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Nuclear Tests. US, French and China Articles, 1960-1971 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Nuclear Tests, Utah (Donnwinders). Anti Nuclear Test Movement, USSR I, 1981-1989 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Nuclear Tests, Utah (Donnwinders). Anti Nuclear Test Movement, USSR II, 1963-1991 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Nuclear War Effects (1981 FAS) (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Nuclear War Effects. "Winter" and Starvation, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1985-1991 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Nuclear Waste Disposal Geological Problems. Transportation, 1977-1990 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Nuclear Waste. New York Dump Battle, 1988-1991 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Nuclear Waste Safe Disposal. PSR Talk May 6, 1992, 1985-2002 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Nuclear Waste Storage Problems, 1977-1983 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Nuclear Weapons Data. NRDC, 1988-1993 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Nuclear Weapons. 3rd Generation, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Nuclear Weapons. History and Battle Against (Video Tape Resources), 1981-1991 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Nuclear Weapons Plant Scandal. 1988-1989. Keith Schneider and Others (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Nuclear Weapons "Pulse" Risk, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Oak Ridge Human Experiments, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Ocean Pollution, 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Ocean Power, 1974-1979 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Office of Technology Assessment (OTA), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 32)